<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-03-15T11:40:17+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Soroush Zendedel</title><subtitle>Explore the harmonies of technology, the melodies of life, and the rhythm of poetry in this multifaceted blog.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to LifeInSync!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/introduction/2024/03/15/welcome-to-lifeinsync.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to LifeInSync!" /><published>2024-03-15T03:33:30+03:30</published><updated>2024-03-15T03:33:30+03:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/introduction/2024/03/15/welcome-to-lifeinsync</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/introduction/2024/03/15/welcome-to-lifeinsync.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="welcome-to-lifeinsync">Welcome to LifeInSync</h1>

<p>Welcome to my personal static blog! I’m thrilled to have you here as we embark on this journey together, exploring the fascinating world of technology through articles, audio podcasts, and video casts.</p>

<p><img src="/assets/images/welcome.gif" alt="Welcome to LifeInSync" /></p>

<h2 id="about-me">About Me</h2>

<p>I’m Soroush Piri Zendedel (سروش پیری زنده دل), your host and curator for this blog. As a passionate programmer, poet, and visual artist, I’m excited to share my diverse interests and creative works with you.</p>

<h2 id="what-to-expect">What to Expect</h2>

<p>Get ready to dive deep into the world of technology! Here, you’ll find a diverse range of content including articles, audio podcasts, and video casts covering topics such as programming languages, software development, tech industry trends, and more.</p>

<h2 id="get-involved">Get Involved</h2>

<p>I believe in the power of community and collaboration. Your input and feedback are invaluable to me, so feel free to engage with the content by leaving comments, asking questions, and sharing your own thoughts and experiences.</p>

<h2 id="stay-connected">Stay Connected</h2>

<p>To stay updated on the latest posts, audio podcasts, and video casts, be sure to subscribe to the blog or follow me on social media. Let’s connect and continue the conversation beyond the blog!</p>

<h2 id="lets-get-started">Let’s Get Started!</h2>

<p>So, without further ado, let’s dive into the world of technology together! Feel free to explore the existing content and don’t hesitate to reach out if you have any questions or suggestions.</p>

<p>Thank you for joining me on this exciting journey, and I look forward to sharing valuable insights and experiences with you!</p>

<p>Happy exploring,
Soroush.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Introduction" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to LifeInSync]]></summary></entry></feed>